<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Taplytics Example</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="mainText">An example app with the Taplytics Android SDK already integrated</string>
    <string name="what_text">What is it?</string>
    <string name="in_action_text">In action.</string>
    <string name="events_button_text">EVENTS</string>

    <!-- Dynamic Variables -->
    <string name="dynamic_variable_text">Taplytics offers variables that can be modified from the Taplytics Dashboard.</string>
    <string name="dynamic_variable_action">Give it a try. If you have entered your API key in the Application class, you can make a new experiment on the Taplytics Dashboard. You should see this new variable there in the dynamic variables tab! Change it\'s value, and use the shake menu to switch variations. \n\n If you don\'t see it in the dashboard, create a variable by the same name!</string>
    <string name="dynamic_variable_button_text">DYNAMIC VARIABLES</string>
    <string name="check_it_out">check it out</string>


    <!-- Code Bloks -->
    <string name="code_block_text">With Taplytics, you can create blocks of code that run or do not run based on the variation!</string>
    <string name="code_block_action">Give it a try. If you have entered your API key in the Application class, you can make a new experiment on the Taplytics Dashboard. You should see this new code block there in the dynamic variables tab! Change whether or not it should run, then shake the phone to switch variations! When it runs, the button below should disappear.  \n\n If you don\'t see it in the dashboard, create a variable by the same name!</string>
    <string name="code_block_button_text">CODE BLOCKS</string>
    <string name="code_block_button">check it out</string>


    <!-- User Attributes -->
    <string name="user_attributes_button_text">USER ATTRIBUTES</string>
    <string name="user_attributes_text">With the SDK, you can pass Taplytics many kinds of user attributes, such as their email, id, gender, age, etc. \n\nYou can also send custom data, such as "paid subscription", or any other json data. \nModify and apply your experiments based on this data! \n\nThis page has sent some basic information to your Taplytics panel, see for yourself!</string>

    <!-- Code Experiments -->
    <string name="events_title">EVENT TRACKING</string>
    <string name="event_text">Taplytics allows you to log unique events that happen within your app. \n\nEvents such as a purchase going through, social sharing, and simple button clicks can be tracked with one small function. </string>
    <string name="event_action">Give it a try, pressing the button will track a button press event, with the number of times its been pressed this session on this screen. </string>
    <string name="send_an_event">send an event</string>


    <!-- Visual Experiments -->
    <string name="visual_experiments_button_text">VISUAL EXPERIMENTS</string>
    <string name="visual_experiment_text">Taplytics allows you to A/B test your app without writing a single line of code using visual experiments.</string>
    <string name="visual_experiment_action">Give it a try. On your Taplytics dashboard, click "add element to variation", and then click an element on the app. \n\nFrom the dashboard, edit the settings on the view, select that variation, and check out your updates live!</string>


</resources>